Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory9 Mss.B.B61.inventory09
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents M
  - Mandelbaum, May (Mrs. Edel) (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 23; 2p.
    - See Robbins, W.J., Dec. 17, 1931.
    - See Boas, F. to National research council Board of fellowships in the biological sciences, Dec. 18, 1931.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 9; 2p.
    - See Boas, F. (open letter) Aug. 19, 1932, 1932 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 27; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 13; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec.; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 20; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 21; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 3; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.end
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.end
    - To Boas, 1936 July 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 4; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1940 July 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. end; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 9; 2p.
  - Maness, I. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1938 May 20; 1p.
  - Manfield, Manuel (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 8; 1p.
  - Mangan, M.A. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 31; 1p.
  - Manges, M. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 7; 1p.
  - Manhattan Delivery Com. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 14
  - Manhattan Storage & Warehouse Co. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 8
  - Manheimer, J.S. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 15; 1p.
  - Mankiewicz, Frank (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas
      - See Prokosch, E., Sept. 11, 1933
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb.; 1p.
      (Enc: Resolution adopted the Association of teachers of German of New York and vicinity)
  - Manly, J.M. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - J.M. Manly -- to M.W. Beckwith, 1923 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc. originally with Beckwith, M.W., May 9, 1923)
  - Mann, A.R. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 4; 1p.
  - Mann, D. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1915 June 14
  - Mann, Edward C. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1888 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, n.d.; 2p.
    - E.C. Mann -- to J.H. Raymond, 1888 Apr. 25; 3p.
  - Mann, Heinrich (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1938; 1p.
  - Mann, J.R. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 3
  - Mann, Thomas (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 May 8; 1p.
  - Mann?, W? (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 29; 2p.
  - Manning, M. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 May 11; 1p.
  - Manning, Rosalie (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 24; 1p.
  - Manning, W.T. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 18; 1p.
  - Manny, F.A. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept. 28
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 25; 2p.
  - Mansfeld, Dr. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1890 Nov. 14; 3p.
  - Mansfield, Howard (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 22
  - Mansfield, Mike (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 28; teleg.
  - Manuscript Myths (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1908; 2p.
  - Marand, Irene (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 14; 1p.
  - Marburg, J. William (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 26; 2p.
  - Marburg, Louis C. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 4; 1p.
  - Marburg?, Louis J. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 13; 1p.
  - Marburg, Theodore H. (Box 60)
    Native American Images note
    Mayan ruins
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 18
  - Marcantonio, Vito (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 3; 1p.
  - Marcel, P. Roland (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 6; 2p.
  - March, B.C. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 2
  - Marcou, P. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 10; 2p.
  - Marcus, B.K. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1928 July 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 17; 1p.
    - (Enc: Marcus, B.K. to Butler, N.M. July 17, 1928. 2 copies.), 1928 July 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - B.K. Marcus -- to N.M. Butler, 1928 July 17; 1p.
    - B.K. Marcus -- to F.D. Fackenthal, 1930 Oct. 6; 1p.
  - Marcuse, M. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 May 17; 1p.
  - Marcuse, R. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 10; 1p.
  - Marett, R.R. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 2; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 15; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc. originally with Boas, F. to Bush, W.T. Oct. 13, 1928, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 6 May 6
    - To Boas, 1912 May 27
    - To Boas, 1912 June 6; postca.
    - To Boas, 1912 July 8; postca.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1914 May 2
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 10; 2p.
  - Margolius, S.S. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 17; 1p.
  - Marimon, R.L. (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Marinello, Juan (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 4; 1p.
  - Marini, M.G. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1928 July 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 7; 1p.
  - Markel, Lester (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept. 25; 1p.
  - Markovits, A.V. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.; 2p.
  - Marks, Louis (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Maron, Sanuel H. (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 20; 1p.
  - Marot, Helen (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 July 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 27; 1p.
  - Marquette, W.G. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 2; 1p.
  - Marrow, A.J. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 July 26; 2p.
  - Marschak (Box 61)
    - From Szilard, 1933 May 9
  - Marsh, Anne W. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec.; 1p.
  - Marsh, Gordon H. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), Nov. 6, 1941.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 13; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 13; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 6; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 1; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 May 17; 1p.
  - Marshall, E. (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 8
  - Marshall, George (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1942 July 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas
      - See Brewster, Dorothy, July 18, 1939.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 13; 1p.
      (Enc: Pritt to Hays cablegram Marshall, G. to Gt. Brit. Ambass. Miller, F.R.H. to Marshall, G. Marshall, G. to Gt. Brit. Ambass.)
    - See Adams, J.T., Apr. 30, 1940.
    - G. Marshall -- from A. Einstein, 1941 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Sept. 12; 2p.
    - G. Marshall -- to Gt. Britain Ambassador, 1940 Feb. 29; 1p.
    - G. Marshall -- to Gt. Britain Ambassador, 1940 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - G. Marshall -- from F.R.H. Miller, 1940 Mar. 4
    - (Enc. with Marshall, G., Mar. 13, 1940)
  - Marshall, James E. (Box 61)
    - J.E. Marshall -- from T.W. Phillips, 1940 July 31
    - (Enc. with Phillips, T.W., Jr., Aug. 8, 1940)
  - Marshall, John (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1934 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 11; 1p.
  - Marshall, Louis (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - L. Marshall -- to E.L. Boas, 1906 Jan. 13; 1p.
  - Marshall, Margaret (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 4; 1p.
  - Marshall, R. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 24; 1p.
  - Marston, Horace M. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 19; 1p.
  - Martha (Box 61)
    See Champion, Martha
  - Martin, Clarence D. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1939 July 7; 2p.
  - Martin, D.S. (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 19; 2p.
  - Martin, F.W. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - (See Boas, F. to Tyler, J.M., Nov. 13, 1919
  - Martin, Gertie (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 10; 2p.
  - Martin, L.J. (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 22
  - Martin, P.A. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 12; 1p.
  - Martin, Paul S. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1939 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p.
  - Martin, Rudolf (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 31; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1912 June 12
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 28; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 28; 2p.
    - Paper on nutrition, 1920 Feb.; 6p.
      - (Enc. with M. Seeliger, Feb. 20, 1922
    - Paper on nutrition, 1922 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - Paper on nutrition, 1922 Dec.; 1p.
    - R. Martin -- to Adolph H. Schultz, 1922 Dec. 7; 3p.
  - Martin, W.R. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 17
  - Martin-Dillon, P.R. (Box 61)
    - To E. Chapman, 1939 May 23; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Chapman, E., May 26, 1939)
  - Martin-Oppenheim, Stefanie (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 25; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Sept. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - (Attached: Notes and drawings), 1936 June 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept. 9; postcard
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 2; 1p.
  - Martine, James E. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 7; 12p.
    - From Boas, 1916 June 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1916 June 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 12
  - Martiner, J. (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 July 1
  - Martinez, Gilberto Crespo y (Box 61)
    See Crespo y Martinez, Gilberto
  - Martiny, T. (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 6; 4p.
  - Marven, D.E.? (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 24
  - Marx, A. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 9; 1p.
  - Marx, Emily (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 13; 1p.
  - Marxhausen, G. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1932 June 2; 1p.
  - Masani, R.P. (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p.
  - Masaryk (Box 61)
    - See Schneiderman, H., June 25, 1934.
  - Maschke, H. (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1899 June 12; 1p.
  - Maschke, T. (Box 61)
    - See Leahy, W.W., 1929 Dec. 31
  - Mason, Gregory (Box 61)
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - G. Mason -- to Thomas Chubb, 1941 Sept. 18; 2p.
  - Mason, J. Alden (Box 61)
    Folders # 11, 12: Mayan.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1906 Sept. 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1911 May 11
    - From Boas, 1911 June 15
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 16
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 21
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 2; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 5; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1915 May 21
    - From Boas, 1915 June 28
    - From Boas, 1915 June 30
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 7
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 18
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 25; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Sept. 22
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 10 and 30
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 May 2
    - To Boas, 1907 May 4
    - To Boas, 1911 June 29
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 10; postc.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 21; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. end
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 6; postca.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 15; post.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 5; post.
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 6; post.
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1912 June 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept. 24
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 23; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 13; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 12; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1913 May 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 July 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 8; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 26; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 19; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 16; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 6; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 May 14; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 July 4; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 July 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 21; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 11; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 1; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 17; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 31; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 5; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 8; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 6; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1916 July 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 13; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 18; 2p.
    - (Enc: List), 1939 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 July 25; 2p.
    - J.A. Mason -- from A.M. Espinosa, 1916 Aug. 17
    - J.A. Mason -- to H.H. Roberts, 1920 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - J.A. Mason -- to Wilbur K. Thomas, 1940 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Wilbur, W.K., Nov. 12, 1940)
    - J.A. Mason -- from W.K. Thomas, 1940 Nov. 7
    - (Enc. with Wilbur, W.K., Nov. 12, 1940)
  - Mason, Max (Box 61)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 26; 1p.
  - Mason, Otis T. (Box 61)
    Inuit woman
    - From Boas, 1887 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1887 May 15
    - From Boas, 1887 June 26
    - From Boas, 1887 Oct. 17
    - From Boas, 1894 May 20
    - From Boas, 1894 June 12
    - From Boas, 1896 June 14
    - From Boas, 1896 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 May 1
    - From Boas, 1908 May 21
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1885 May 23
    - To Boas, 1887 May 19
    - To Boas, 1887 June 24
    - To Boas, 1887 June 29
    - To Boas, 1887 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1887 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 2
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 May 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1890 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1890 Sept. 10
    - To Boas, 1890 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1893 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1894 June 4
    - To Boas, 1894 July 25
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1895 June 5
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1896 May 7
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1897 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 May 4
    - To Boas, 1908 May 23
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts
    - See Dayton, Neil A., 6-12-36, 6-23-36, 6-29-36
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology
    See Buerger, M.J.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 3; telegram
  - Masthall?, Charles C.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 5; 3p.
  - Mather, K.F. (Box 62)
    - To D. Johnson, 1931 Apr. 14; 1p.
  - Mathews, F.S. (Box 62)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 23; 2p.
  - Mathews, S. (Box 62)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 8
  - Mathiassen, T. (Box 62)
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 14; 3p.
  - Mathis, E.M. (Box 62)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 20; 1p.
  - Matiegka, J. (Box 62)
    - From Boas, 1922 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 9; 2p.
  - Matlegka, H. (Box 62)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p.
  - Matorin, N. (Box 62)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 23; 1p.